const List<Map<String, dynamic>> gapFillingSetUpData = [
  {
    "exercise_id": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "game_key": 5,
    "description": "Fill gaps with article: a, an, the, - (for no article)"
  },
  {
    "exercise_id": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "game_key": 5,
    "description": "Fill gaps in popular proverbs with one word"
  },
  {
    "exercise_id": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "game_key": 5,
    "description": "Fill gaps with one word"
  },
  {
    "exercise_id": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "game_key": 5,
    "description": "Fill gaps in popular proverbs with one word"
  },
];


const List<Map<String, dynamic>> gapFillingQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "_ tigers are dangerous animals.",
    "answer": "-",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 1,
  },
  {
    "question": "_ children from my class have all got flu!",
    "answer": "the",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 2,
  },
  {
    "question": "I spent the last summer in _ London and we visited the Big Ben.",
    "answer": "-",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 3,
  },
  {
    "question": "I hope you enjoy _ results of our hard work.",
    "answer": "the",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 4,
  },
  {
    "question": "You should go to _ bed. You have to wake up tomorrow in the morning.",
    "answer": "-",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 5,
  },
  {
    "question": "_ Vistula is the biggest river in Poland.",
    "answer": "The",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 6,
  },
  {
    "question": "_ music always helps me to relax in the evening.",
    "answer": "-",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 7,
  },
  {
    "question": "I hated _ music that was played last night at the party.",
    "answer": "the",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 8,
  },
  {
    "question": "Let's go to _ grocery. We only have few onions left!",
    "answer": "the",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 9,
  },
  {
    "question": "_ pollution is a big problem in our city.",
    "answer": "-",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 10,
  },
  {
    "question": "I often feel bad because of _  pollution in out city.",
    "answer": "the",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 11,
  },
  {
    "question": "_ United States is the fourth biggest country in the world.",
    "answer": "The",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 12,
  },
  {
    "question": "Madrid is _ capital of Spain.",
    "answer": "the",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 13,
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm _ surgeon. I save people's lives.",
    "answer": "a",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 14,
  },
  {
    "question": "I had _ lunch in a restaurant today.",
    "answer": "-",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 15,
  },
  {
    "question": "He came here _ hour ago.",
    "answer": "an",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_1",
    "question_id": 16,
  },
  {
    "question": "Absence makes the _ grow fonder",
    "answer": "heart",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 17,
  },
  {
    "question": "There is no place like _",
    "answer": "home",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 18,
  },
  {
    "question": "_ is money",
    "answer": "Time",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 19,
  },
  {
    "question": "When in Rome, do as the _ do",
    "answer": "Romans",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 20,
  },
  {
    "question": "Keep your friends close, and your enemies _",
    "answer": "closer",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 21,
  },
  {
    "question": "Easy _, easy go",
    "answer": "come",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 22,
  },
  {
    "question": "Don’t judge a book by its _",
    "answer": "cover",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 23,
  },
  {
    "question": "Better _ than never",
    "answer": "late",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 24,
  },
  {
    "question": "A watched pot never _",
    "answer": "boils",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 25,
  },
  {
    "question": "Actions speak louder than _.",
    "answer": "words",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 26,
  },
  {
    "question": "Knowledge is _",
    "answer": "power",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 27,
  },
  {
    "question": "No man is an _",
    "answer": "island",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 28,
  },
  {
    "question": "The early _ gets the worm",
    "answer": "bird",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 29,
  },
  {
    "question": "Two _ don’t make a right",
    "answer": "wrongs",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 30,
  },
  {
    "question": "Where there’s smoke, there’s _",
    "answer": "fire",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 31,
  },
  {
    "question": "You can lead a _ to water, but you can’t make him drink it",
    "answer": "horse",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 32,
  },
  {
    "question": "The enemy of my _ is my friend",
    "answer": "enemy",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_2",
    "question_id": 33,
  },
  {
    "question": "She is a famous director _ films won Oscar award last year.",
    "answer": "whose",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 34,
  },
  {
    "question": "It's not allowed to eat _ the exam",
    "answer": "during",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 35,
  },
  {
    "question": "We won't send you this order  _ you make the payment in advance",
    "answer": "unless",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 36,
  },
  {
    "question": "We have lived in this village  _ ten years.",
    "answer": "for",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 37,
  },
  {
    "question": "My dad died five years _",
    "answer": "ago",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 38,
  },
  {
    "question": "When did you _ work yesterday?",
    "answer": "leave",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 39,
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the students _ not submitted his homework.",
    "answer": "has",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 40,
  },
  {
    "question": "Neither Ann nor Suzy _ at the party.",
    "answer": "was",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 41,
  },
  {
    "question": "He is junior _ to me.",
    "answer": "to",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 42,
  },
  {
    "question": "He has _ knowledge about biology",
    "answer": "little",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_3",
    "question_id": 43,
  },
  {
    "question": "Beauty is only _ deep.",
    "answer": "skin",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 1,
  },
  {
    "question": "Don’t bite the _ that feeds you.",
    "answer": "hand",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 2,
  },
  {
    "question": "Every _ has his price",
    "answer": "man",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 3,
  },
  {
    "question": "Good things come to those who _.",
    "answer": "wait",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 4,
  },
  {
    "question": "If you can’t _ them, join them.",
    "answer": "beat",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 5,
  },
  {
    "question": "It’s no use _ over spilt milk.",
    "answer": "crying",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 6,
  },
  {
    "question": "Necessity is the mother of _.",
    "answer": "invention",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 7,
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of _, out of mind.",
    "answer": "sight",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 8,
  },
  {
    "question": "Two _ are better than one.",
    "answer": "heads",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 9,
  },
  {
    "question": "You can’t have your _ and eat it too.",
    "answer": "cake",
    "exercise_key": "Game_5_ex_4",
    "question_id": 10,
  }
];

// https://www.adelaide.edu.au/english-for-uni/articles/exercise-3-articles-gap-fill
// https://usefulenglish.ru/grammar/articles-exercise-two